[Music]
[Música]
and
y
and much
y mucho
no
no
enrique his little thing says to maria patiño he
enrique su cosita dice a maría patiño se
makes her [ __ ] clapping
le hace el [__] palmas
that expression
esa expresión
that organic expression he makes her
esa expresión orgánica se le hace el
[ __ ] clapping to maria patricio he
[__] palmas a maría patricio se le
makes her [ __ ] clapping with his
hace el [__] palmas con su teoría
conspiracy theory leftover davis marta
conspiranoica sobrante davis marta
I risk seeing very put we would go
arriesgo a ver muy puesta iríamos
up it was
levanta era
because it suits everyone
porque le conviene a todos y
[Music]
[Música]
plays with the ambiguity of the date
juega con la ambigüedad de la fecha
now he's going to start defending
ahora se va a poner a defender a la
ration carrasco from the raffle so much in
ración carrasco del tómbola tanto en la
life the year 2010
vida el año 2010
this already makes me feel sorry for maria patiño sean maria
esto ya me da pena maría patiño sean
patiño you have was without equal
maría patiño tú has estaba sin igual de
standing affirmed predisposed you on the set
pie afirmó predispuesta tú en el plató
of sálvame with antonella I saw
de sálvame con antonella vi al lado
turia sitting next to you and you saying that rocio
turia sentada y tú diciendo que la rocío
carrasco went crazy she's rolled for
carrasco se volvió loca es enrollo por
a bunch of guys in one summer and I sing
un montón de tíos en un verano y canto
in life rolling with no one and now
en la vida de rollo con ninguna y ahora
you're rolling with a hammer what follows what a
estás tú a de martillo que sigue a que
hammer that they're going to renew your
vaya martillo que te van a renovar
contract at the television factory until
contrato en la fábrica de la tele hasta
you want a little
quieres de un poco
[Music]
[Música]
and why
y por qué
but that Marta has protected risk for
pero que ha protegido marta riesgo para
Patiño that here was protected Marta
patiño que aquí era protegió marta
risk if this morning he has
riesgo si esta misma mañana le ha
answered a message to the companions
contestado un mensaje a los compañeros
saying that you can not deny the
diciendo que no se puede negar lo
obvious
evidente
if he had wanted to protect it he would have
si lo hubiera querido proteger hubiera
said many times that he came here to
dicho muchas veces que vino aquí a
have a coffee
tomarse un café
listen to me that he left the
escúchame que se dejó el cargador del
cell phone charger in the car
móvil en el coche
that he has protected
que ha protegido
here I am not going to
aquí no te voy a
[Music]
[Música]
but
pero
and
y
[Music]
[Música]
and I what the truth
y yo lo que la verdad
once
una vez
since
desde
and already
y ya
sometimes
a veces
hehehe
jejeje
like Antonio Avila already real to a ring to
como antonio ávila ya real a un anillo a
Marta disco
marta disco
this is a parody for the minors
esta es una parodia por los menores
listen to me like Antonia says she has
escúchame como antonia dice la haya
done that is that it gives a little salt is
hecho eso es que da un poquito de sal es
a little women so it is true that the
un poco mujeres así que es verdad que la
la la
la la
the fact itself can fit a little
el hecho en sí puede cuadrar un poco
because a little boom in
porque un poco boom en
or rather the fact could fit a little
o sea el hecho podría cuadrar un poco
with Antonio Davis for the green the matter
con antonio davis por lo verde el asunto
is to give a ring to a chick because
es regalarle un anillo a una pava porque
to an engagement
a un compromiso
[Laughter]
[Risas]
what was
qué
missing I would be  divine
me faltó yo sería divino
and alive
y viva
and now
y ahora
[Music] if she
[Música]
is hurt with the credibility thing she
está dolida con lo de la credibilidad
is hurt by the one who does not have it
está dolida de la que no la tiene
expresses that you do not have it
expresa que no la tienes
Mariah Patina is a 4x4 when it comes to
mariah patina es una 4x4 a la hora de
becoming Latina when you are staying with
hacerse latina cuando estás quedando con
10 percent in terms of seriousness and
10 por ciento a nivel de seriedad y
proceeds yes yes but it is that I like it
procede sí sí pero es que a mí me gusta
because she is already very put I will
porque ya se pone muy puesta siempre voy
always be like that
a ser siempre así
credibility to the one who does
credibilidad
not have it that does not have it regret that it does not matter that
al que no la tiene que no la tiene pesar
what I have told you
que da igual que de lo que te he dicho
even if David appears around with seven
aunque aparezca en torno david con siete
women there at the Jesus Gil in a
mujeres allí a los jesús gil en una
pool that it does not matter that that does not take away
piscina que da igual que eso no quita
that you are lying and that you give false information
que tú miente y que da información falsa
that it does not matter what Antonio David does I
que da igual lo que haga antonio david
am going to make it worse for you even if
os lo voy a poner peor aunque el día de
tomorrow it is proven that Rocío Carrasco
mañana se demostrara que rocío carrasco
was right and what Rocío
tenía la razón y lo que decía rocío
Carrasco said is still unnecessary in the truth that would
carrasco sobran todavía en la verdad eso
not give credibility to Maria Patiño
no le daría credibilidad a maría patiño
that several Patiño do not have nor the
que no la tienen varias patiño ni la
low to have that it does not matter that you do not
baja tener que da igual que no te
understand that she has no credibility because she
enteras que no tiene credibilidad porque
gives false information because she lies
da información falsa porque miente
because today she says hi tomorrow she says go  about the
porque hoy dice hi mañana dice ve sobre
same thing that doesn't matter it
lo mismo que da igual
remains the same that he doesn't have it and
queda igual que no la tiene y se pone
so it goes my life
así mi vida
that is hurting because of
que le está dolida por lo de
credibility he knows is hurt and he doesn't stop
credibilidad sabe está dolida y no para
repeating it over and over again he posted a
de repetirlo una y otra vez ha puesto un
tweet because my sources I don't know what they say
tuit porque mis fuentes no sé qué dicen
about the source he put a
de fuente ha puesto un
bit to the answer from Rocío Floresta she
cuanto a la respuesta de rocío floresta
told me that it doesn't matter that what she doesn't
me lo dijo que da igual que lo que no no
Maria Patiño doesn't understand and what she doesn't
se entera maría patiño y lo que no
understand is that she has to put the
entiende es que tiene que poner la p
capital p on her twitter that it's
mayúscula en su twitter que me está
bothering me it's screwing up my life
molestando que me está jodiendo la vida
that she writes with a lowercase letter your name is
que escriba con minúscula tu nombre
okay and what Maria Patiño doesn't understand
vale y que lo que no entiende maría
is that it doesn't matter even if Antonio
patiño es que da igual aunque antonio
Ávila was proven to be the devil
ávila se demostrara que fuera el [__]
even if they condemn Antonio David it
aunque condenarán antonio david de
really doesn't matter that he is not the
verdad que da igual que no es es el
reason that the reason is that you have no
motivo que el motivo es que no tienes
credibility that your opinion is worthless
credibilidad que tu opinión no vale
and the turkey doesn't understand man wouldn't it be like
y no se entera la pava tío no sería como
saying things
decir las cosas
that she doesn't understand man it doesn't matter that she doesn't
que no se entera tío que da igual que no
have it
la tiene
she comes to the gas station
ella viene a la gasera
[Music]
[Música]
lives and sits down turns around and
vive y se sienta se da la vuelta y se
sits down as if the scene were very epic
sienta como si la escena fuera muy épica
how pathetic  This is it, but it is Fernando,
qué patético es esto pero sí es fernando
the councilor who sent me, I applauded several
el regidor que ha mandado aplaudí varias
times during the
patiño
5 hours of humidity
5 horas de humedades
[Music]
[Música]